creators.com 2011-04-28

# Creators.com Privacy Policy

We at Creators.com respect our visitors' right to privacy, and we understand that our visitors are concerned about maintaining the privacy of their personal information. Creators.com is committed to protecting your privacy; we do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

**Creators.com use of e-mail addresses:**

Your e-mail address will be used by Creators.com to provide you with content that you have specifically requested to receive, as well as information about services or products from third parties that we feel would be of interest to you. We will not disclose any of your personal information to such third parties when we do this. Though we hope you gain value from all the messages you receive, you may opt-out of these e-mails at any time by following the instructions provided at the end of each e-mail.

**Creators.com use of personal information:**

We will collect your personal information only when you voluntarily provide it. All voluntary submission of information to this website will become the property of Creators Syndicate. Creators.com is the sole owner of any information collected on any portion of the website. This information will only be used to provide services you have requested, such as e-mail alerts or sending content to a friend.

We may disclose personally identifiable information to third parties when required by law or in the event such information is relevant to judicial or government investigations or proceedings, or otherwise necessary to protect our website or the safety of its users. Finally, Creators.com may also use information obtained from cookies to perform statistical analysis of aggregate user behavior, but personally identifiable information will not be used in that instance. We may use that information for internal purposes to improve content and design, and share it, in aggregate only, with partners. 

**E-mail delivery:**

If you register with our site requesting e-mail updates when a portion of the site is updated, we may contact you at this email address from time to time with informative messages about our services that we believe may be of interest to you, such as new features or added content. If you wish to e-mail a friend to invite them to view content on Creators.com, we will ask you for the friend's name and e-mail address. Creators.com will then send a one-time e-mail to this address inviting them to visit the page that you selected. Creators.com may store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail. The friend may contact Creators.com at any time to request the removal of their information from the database.

**Movement through the site:**

Creators.com uses server logs to track the path of visitors to our site. We use this information solely to improve visitors' experience on our site and to enhance the site's navigability and ease of use.

**Links to other sites:**

Creators.com contains links, including advertisements, to websites not related to or affiliated with Creators.com or Creators Syndicate. Creators.com is not responsible for the privacy policies of these outside websites, nor is Creators.com responsible for the content of these sites.

**With respect to Ad Servers:**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit Creators.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Use of Materials from Creators.com:**

All materials reproduced on this site remain the property of Creators Syndicate, and are intended for the user's personal use only. Any reproduction, transmission, performance, display or editing of these materials by any means mechanical or electronic without the express written permission of Creators Syndicate is strictly prohibited. If you wish to reproduce any content that appears on this site in any way, you must contact us via a permission request form [here](http://www.creators.com/permission-requests.html). Please note that Far Side® cartoons may not be used in any electronic format, and therefore may not be posted on websites for any reason. For more information about this policy, please see this [note from Gary Larson](http://www.creators.com/a-note-from-gary-larson.html).

This privacy policy was last updated on April 14, 2011.
